Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/chaitalirajurkar (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL

Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel

Certifications

Online Marketing Foundations
Google AdWords Essential Training
SQL Tips, Tricks, & Techniques
Google Analytics Essential Training
Introduction to R

Honors-Awards

Campus Associate of the Quarter

Chaitali Rajurkar

Seeking full-time opportunities as Data Analyst/Data Scientist with SQL, Statistics, R, Tableau, Python, Excel expertise Fullerton, California

Summary

- Three years of experience in Cognizant Technology Solutions as a Programmer/Salesforce Analyst working on Salesforce platform for CRM (Customer Relationship Management) domain.
- Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology from MIT College of Engineering, Pune, India.

Skills: Data Analytics, Data Mining, Statistical Analysis, Business Intelligence, Salesforce, Data Visualization, Business Requirement Gathering, Business Process Development

Programming Skills: Structured Query Language (SQL), R Programming, Apex, Java, HTML, CSS, Python (Pandas, NumPy, SciPy, matplotlib)

Analytical Tools: R Studio, SPSS, Tableau.

Microsoft Office: Excel (Advanced - Pivot Tables, V-lookups, Macros, VBA), Project, Visio

Salesforce.com: Apex Class, Visualforce, Triggers, Einstein Analytics (Wave), Workflows, Process Builder, Salesforce Reports And Dashboards,

Databases: Oracle, MySQL, SQL Server, MS Access

Experience

California State University, Fullerton Graduate Teaching Assistant August 2018 - May 2019 (10 months)

Fullerton, California

- Provide assistance to the faculty and Department Chair in searching for, collecting, and arranging data and literature.
- Help students facing difficulty in working with MS Excel.
- Conducting supplemental instruction classes for the undergraduates at
 Cal State to help them in Statistics for topics like Hypothesis Testing, Linear
 Regression, etc.
- Assist faculty with evaluating student work, examinations, and other duties as assigned.
- Assist in the departmental office by providing guidance and information.

Cognizant

Programmer Analyst September 2014 - July 2017 (2 years 11 months)

Pune Area, India

- Managed and guided a team of four to deliver the 'project initiation' module.
- Performed tasks like requirement analysis, development, and implementation of code and writing SQL queries and fetching required data from the database.
- Utilized Salesforce to develop business solutions and spreadsheets for managing the project's master data.
- Prepared and maintained documentation of the various business proposals using MS Word.
- Created weekly status reports keeping track of tasks assigned to team members.
- Communicated with team members for updates regarding the daily activities via emails and meetings.
- Awarded with 'Campus Associate of the Quarter' for my contributions to this project.

Education

California State University, Fullerton

Master's degree, Information Science/Studies · (2017 - 2019)

University of Pune

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.), Information Technology (2010 - 2014)